https://www.floristssupply.com/privacy-policy/

Vancouver
Roseberry Square, Unit 5, 3979 Marine Way, Burnaby BC, V5J 5E3
Vancouver
Roseberry Square, Unit 5, 3979 Marine Way, Burnaby BC, V5J 5E3
604.630.4688
1.866.203.8607
More info
Privacy Policy
At Florists Supply Ltd., safeguarding your confidentiality and protecting your personal information is of primary concern. We are committed to meeting or exceeding all applicable laws and regulations and privacy standards established at law, including Canada’s Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (the “Act”). As part of this commitment, Florists Supply Ltd. has followed the ten privacy principles described in the Act to govern our actions as they relate to the use of personal information. The ten privacy principles, and how they apply to us, are as follows:
Principle 1 – Accountability. Florists Supply Ltd. is responsible for maintaining and protecting any personal information under our control. In fulfilling this mandate, Florists Supply Ltd. has designated an individual who is accountable for our compliance with these ten privacy principles.
Principle 2 – Identifying Purposes. The purposes for which personal information is collected shall be identified before or at the time the information is collected.
Principle 3 – Consent. Your knowledge and consent is required for the collection, use or disclosure of personal information except where required or permitted by law.
Principle 4 – Limiting Collection. The personal information collected must be limited to those details necessary for the purposes identified by Florists Supply Ltd. Information must be collected by fair and lawful means.
Principle 5 – Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention. Your personal information may only be used or disclosed for the purpose for which it was collected unless you otherwise consent, or when it is required or permitted by law. Your personal information may only be retained for the period of time required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected.
Principle 6 – Accuracy. Your personal information must be maintained in as accurate, complete and up-to-date form as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is to be used.
Principle 7 – Safeguarding Personal information. Your personal information must be protected by security safeguards that are appropriate to the sensitivity level of the information.
Principle 8 – Openness. Florists Supply Ltd. is required to make information available to you concerning the policies and practices that apply to the management of your personal information.
Principle 9 – Customer Access. Upon request, you shall be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of your information, and shall be given access to it. You may verify the accuracy and completeness of the information, and may request that it be amended, if appropriate.
Principle 10 – Handling Customer Complaints and Suggestions. You may direct any questions or enquires with respect to the privacy principles outlined herein, or about our privacy practices, by contacting Florists Supply Ltd’s Privacy Officer.
The guidelines below set forth the principles we use in gathering, using, maintaining and protection personal information you provide us.
The Types of Personal Information We Collect
Florists Supply Ltd. gathers and uses only such information that is necessary for providing or enhancing our products and services. Typically, this includes the following personal information:
Your personal and corporate identifying information, including but not limited to contact name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone numbers, demographic and profile data, and internet protocol (IP) address, and your personal and corporate financial information, including but not limited to credit card information (including card type and number, expiry date and name of card holder), banking information (including transit and account numbers), guarantor information, credit references, and credit history information;
The choice to provide us with personal information is always yours. However, your decision to withhold particular details may limit the products and services we are able to provide and make it more difficult for us to advise you or provide services. If we are unable to accommodate your request based on the information that has been provided, we may ask for additional details in order to identify other ways to be of assistance. We will also maintain file histories and other records regarding your corporate and personal information.
We may also collect anonymous/non-personal information. Anonymous/non-personal information is information that cannot be associated with or traced back to a specific individual or business entity.
The Purposes for which we use Personal Information
We use your personal information to communicate with you, help administer our website, diagnose problems with our server, enhance and personalize your visit to our website, display products and content that we feel might be of interest to you, assess your creditworthiness, allow processing of your orders, and effectively provide the products and services you have requested. We may provide your personal information to an affiliated company in order to provide our goods and services to you. We may use your personal information to offer additional products and services sold by Florists Supply Ltd. In the event of a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Florists Supply Ltd., records containing personal information may be transferred to the purchaser.We will not furnish your personal information to an outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your prior consent.This website is for the use of our customers and not for the use of anyone under the age of 18. We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about children. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children. We do not give children the ability to order products. We do not entice children with games or contests.We only use your personal information for the purposes that we have disclosed to you. If for any reason your information is required to fulfill a different purpose, we will notify you and ask you for your consent before we proceed.In some instances such as a legal proceeding or court order, we may also be required to disclose certain information to authorities. Only the information specifically requested is disclosed and we will take precautions to satisfy ourselves that the authorities who are making the request have legitimate grounds to do so.There are some situations where we are legally permitted to disclose personal information such as employing reasonable and legal methods to collect a delinquent account, a medical emergency, or suspicion of illegal activities.We sometimes contract outside organizations to perform specialized services. Our trusted service suppliers may at times be responsible for processing and handling some of the personal information we have received from you.When you visit our website, information is not collected that could identify you personally unless you choose to provide it voluntarily. You are welcome to browse our website at any time anonymously and privately without revealing any personal information about yourself.
Security Measures
We use current technologies and maintain security standards to ensure that your personal information is protected against unauthorized access, disclosure, inappropriate alteration or misuse. All safety and security measures are also appropriate to the sensitivity level of your information. Electronic client files are kept in a secured environment with restricted access. Paper-based files are stored in restricted access areas.We manage our server environment appropriately and our firewall infrastructure is strictly adhered to. Our security practices are reviewed periodically and we employ current technologies to assist us in protecting the confidentiality and privacy of your information.In the course of daily operations, we attempt to restrict access to personal information to authorized employees who have a legitimate business purpose and reason for accessing it. All employees are expected to maintain the confidentiality of personal information at all times and failing to do so will result in appropriate disciplinary measures, which may include dismissal.
Accessing and Amending Your Information
Decisions are often made based on the information we have. Therefore, it is important that your personal information is accurate and complete. As a customer, you have the right to access, verify and amend the information held in your personal and financial files.To help us keep your personal information up-to-date, we encourage you to amend inaccuracies and make corrections as often as necessary. Despite our efforts, errors sometimes do occur. Should you identify any incorrect or out-of-date information in your file(s), we will make the proper changes and provide you with a copy of the corrected information. Where appropriate, we will communicate these changes to other parties who may have unintentionally received incorrect information from us.
Privacy Officer
Customers may direct any questions or enquires with respect to our practices or your personal information by contacting our Privacy Officer, as follows:
FLORISTS SUPPLY LTD.35 Airport Rd, Winnipeg, MB R3H 0V5Attention: PRIVACY OFFICERTelephone No.: 1-800-665-7378Facsimile No.: 1-888-694-6858E-Mail: enquiries@floristssupply.com
Updating this Policy
Any changes to our privacy policy and information handling practices shall be acknowledged in this policy in a timely manner. We may add, modify or remove portions of this policy when we feel it is appropriate to do so.
Inventory Details
Inventory quantities are updated every 1 hour.Please contact a Customer Service Representative for Rush Orders.These terms last updated: May 2015
